{
    "subject": "Prince_Franz_of_Bavaria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_Isabella_Antonie_of_Cro\u00ff",
    "human_readable": "Prince Franz of Bavaria is married to Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886234998703003,
            "question": "Is there a marriage connection between Prince Franz of Bavaria and Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9748997688293457,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Prince Franz of Bavaria and Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9591047167778015,
            "question": "What is the name of the prince who is married to Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9547737836837769,
            "question": "Who is Prince Franz of Bavaria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9506106972694397,
            "question": "Who is Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9495037198066711,
            "question": "Is Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9485313296318054,
            "question": "Name the wife of Prince Franz of Bavaria."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8262416124343872,
            "question": "To whom is Prince Franz of Bavaria connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49870753288269043,
            "question": "What is the name of Princess Isabella Antonie's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44175437092781067,
            "question": "What is the surname of Princess Isabella Antonie's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prince Franz of Bavaria is married to Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff.",
            "html": "yago_26200_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Princess Isabella Antonie's family?",
            "html": "yago_26200_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Prince Franz of Bavaria connected?",
            "html": "yago_26200_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the wife of Prince Franz of Bavaria.",
            "html": "yago_26200_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26200_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Prince Franz of Bavaria and his marriage to Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff, including the date (1912) and location (Schloss Weilburg in Baden near Vienna, Austria). This supports the statement that Prince Franz of Bavaria is married to Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}